

Lawal Usman

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Lagos, Nigeria

creativeludio@gmail.com

☐ ludiousman.github.io

in @ludiousman

PROFILE

Graphic Designer with 5 years of experience in creating stunning designs for clients across various industries. Proficient Adobe Creative Suite, Corel Graphic Suite, etc. Specializes in logo banner design. Passionate about creating designs that are both visually appealing effective communicating the message.

SKILLS

Graphic Designing

•••••

Problem Solving

•••••

Creativity

•••••

Leadership

•••••

WORK EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER AND TYPESETTER

TSD Digital Concept

Oct 2021 - 2023

- Comes up with unique graphic designs for clients.
- Managing multiple design projects simultaneously and meeting deadlines.
- Proofreading and editing designs for accuracy and clarity.
- Creating and editing images and graphics using software such as Photoshop or Illustrator.
- Creating visual designs for print and digital media, such as logos, brochures, websites, and social media posts.
- Developing design concepts and presenting them to clients for approval
- and many more

GRAPHIC DESIGN INTERN

Smartfolks Computer Institute Feb. 2019-2021

- Creating visually appealing infographics to communicate complex information in a simple and engaging way.
- Creating graphics and visuals for social media platforms such as Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Software Engineering

November 2021- till date

Al-hikmah University, Ilorin

Oloye Comprehensive College, Lagos

Dec 2014 -Dec 2020

SOFTWARES I USE

- Adobe Photoshop
- CorelDraw
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe After Effect
- Canva
- Microsoft Office